1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records 6347
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series V. News Clippings and Union Handouts, 1968-2019; 1949-2019
  - District 1199 (NYC), Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - District 1199C - Philadelphia, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - District 1199E - Baltimore - Washington DC, Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - District 1199P - Pennsylvania, Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Ethos, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Greeting Cards, Undated (Box 33, Folder 79)
  - Guardian, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Hats, Undated (Box 33, Folder 78)
  - Hospital Corp. of America, Undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Hughes Report, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - In the Nation, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - In These Times, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - IWW Songbooks (2), Undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Labor/Political Cartoons, Undated (Box 33, Folder 75)
  - Logos, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Many Faces of Local 1199: A Booklet for New Members, Undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - New American Movement, Undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - New Women's Times, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - News Articles from Multiple Sources, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, Correspondence - Misc. Sources, Undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Newsweek, Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Occupational Safety & Health Issues, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Perspectives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Plant closings, Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Progressive, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rochester Council on Occupational Safety and Health (ROCOSH), Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rochester Patriot, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
  - Rochester Progressive Movement, Undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Safety in the Lab Handouts, Undated (Box 33, Folder 74)
  - Songs, Poems, and Quotes, Undated (Box 33, Folder 76)
  - Spectrum, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
  - Stickers and Patches, Undated (Box 33, Folder 77)
  - Undated News Clippings (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - Undercurrent, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Union Basics Handouts (Misc.), Undated (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - United Furniture Workers, Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Vocations for Social Change, Undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Workers World, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)